{
    "subject": "resource/Sir_Charles_Carteret,_3rd_Baronet",
    "predicate": "property/title",
    "object": "resource/List_of_Bailiffs_of_Jersey",
    "human_readable": "The title of Sir Charles Carteret, 3rd Baronet is List of Bailiffs of Jersey.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9591646790504456,
            "question": "What is the title of Sir Charles Carteret, 3rd Baronet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8663997650146484,
            "question": "What can we learn about Jersey from the title of Sir Charles Carteret, 3rd Baronet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8490656614303589,
            "question": "Who might have compiled the list of Bailiffs of Jersey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8040282726287842,
            "question": "Can you name a historical figure who might be on the list of Bailiffs of Jersey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8008144497871399,
            "question": "What does the list of Bailiffs of Jersey contain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7857372760772705,
            "question": "Is Sir Charles Carteret associated with a specific role in Jersey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.723940372467041,
            "question": "What kind of document or record is 'List of Bailiffs of Jersey'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7023373246192932,
            "question": "Who was the 3rd Baronet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17913365364074707,
            "question": "What does the term 'Baronet' signify?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.045341018587350845,
            "question": "What is the significance of 'List' in the context of historical records?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The title of Sir Charles Carteret, 3rd Baronet is List of Bailiffs of Jersey.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2594_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does the term 'Baronet' signify?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2594_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the 3rd Baronet?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2594_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of document or record is 'List of Bailiffs of Jersey'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2594_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2594_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2594_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2594_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2594_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2594_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2594_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2594_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2594_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2594_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2594_54.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provide information about a person named Sir George Carteret (not Charles), who was a royalist statesman, Treasurer of the Navy, and Bailiff of Jersey. However, there is no mention of a Sir Charles Carteret or his title as List of Bailiffs of Jersey."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided do not contain any information related to the title \"List of Bailiffs of Jersey\" or directly connect Sir Charles Carteret, 3rd Baronet to the Bailiff of Jersey position. The texts focus on Sir George Carteret and his roles but do not provide relevant details for Sir Charles Carteret, 3rd Baronet."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Sir Charles Carteret was the Bailiff of Jersey from 1643-1651, but he died in 1680, and there were subsequent Bailiffs after him, so he cannot be listed as a List of Bailiffs of Jersey.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text focuses on Sir George Carteret's life and role as Bailiff of Jersey,  making no mention of a Sir Charles Carteret or any connection to the title of Bailiff of Jersey.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Sir Charles Carteret, 3rd Baronet is not mentioned anywhere in the provided context information as a Bailiff of Jersey.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context provides information about Sir George Carteret (1610\u20131680) serving as Bailiff of Jersey, and does not mention any Sir Charles Carteret 3rd Baronet holding the office. Therefore, it's incorrect to assume that a later title holder was a previous Bailiff of Jersey.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}